Guide to the Dick Thornburgh Papers, 1932- AIS.1998.30.09
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Campaign for Governor of Pennsylvania, 1978; IX.
  - Campaign in Progress, 4.
    The Volunteers files document the particularly active volunteer organization, including lists of volunteers, phone bank schedules and letters of thanks to those who participated in the winning campaign. The strength and success of the volunteer effort was a major component in Thornburgh's victory.
    The County files contain information on each Pennsylvanian county with notes regarding local issues of concern that the Thornburgh/Scranton campaign would address when in the area.
    The Scheduling files include both Dick Thornburgh and Ginny Thornburgh's schedules, as well as invitations, background information, and letters of regret. There is no better place to see the intensity of the commitment demanded of candidates and their families.
    The Media files include information on the media organizations in Pennsylvania that played a vital part in the campaign. There are Thornburgh and Scranton bios and accomplishments, as well as TV and radio ad scripts, newspaper clippings, and sample press kits.
    The Contributors files include information on the contributions made to the Thornburgh-Scranton campaign. They include press releases announcing contributions made to date, fund raising information and finance letters. The success of the fundraising was a critical campaign component.
    There are four separate groupings of correspondence files. The first, "correspondence and subject files," was generated from 1977 through 1978, in Thornburgh's office at Kirkpatrick and Lockhart. Most of the pre-campaign correspondence was necessarily handled through his office, although as the election progressed more was handled by campaign staff. There is also a section of law firm subject files, related to his legal work.
    The second and third sections of correspondence are to and from groups, or to and from individuals. This covers the period from Thornburgh's candidacy announcement (January, 1978) through the election (November, 1978).
    The fourth, "Thornburgh correspondence," is both campaign-related and personal. The letters are all from Mr. Thornburgh, unlike the first two groups, which include both letters to Thornburgh as well as responses from him. This section covers only March 28, 1977 through October 28, 1977.
    Campaign Ephemera files include the familiar brochures and handouts from both the Primary and General Election. These relate to both Dick Thornburgh and to the campaign of Pete Flaherty. Also included are buttons, bumper stickers, complete newspapers from both the primary and general elections, and other miscellaneous items.
    - Organization
      - Campaign staff, Primary, January-May, 1978 (Box 61, Folder 1)
      - Campaign staff, General, June-November, 1978 (Box 61, Folder 2)
      - Finances: Budget matters for Primary 1978, Expense Analysis and Expenditures, January-May, 1978 (Box 61, Folder 3)
      - Office matters and memos, 1977-1978 (Box 61, Folder 4)
      - Regarding Election Law Violations 1977, legal opinions, memos and correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 61, Folder 5)
      - Impoundment petition, Primary, January-May, 1978 (Box 61, Folder 6)
      - Elections Bureau, Department of State: correspondence, regulations, calendar, 1978 (Box 61, Folder 7)
      - Stationery samples, 1977-1978 (Box 61, Folder 8)
      - Primary mailings and forms, January-May, 1978 (Box 61, Folder 9)
      - General mailings and forms, June-November, 1978 (Box 61, Folder 10)
      - Thank you letters, 1977-1978 (Box 61, Folder 11)
      - Lists, memos, mailings to Thornburgh and Thornburgh-Scranton County Chairmen from Thornburgh and staff, 1977-1978 (Box 61, Folder 12)
      - County Chairman manual, 1977-1978 (Box 61, Folder 13)
      - GOP Committee Chairmen 1978, lists, correspondence, memos, 1977-1978 (Box 61, Folder 14)
      - GOP Committee person instructions, Registration Project 1977, 1977-1978 (Box 61, Folder 15)
      - Physicians for Thornburgh-Scranton, Physicians/Republican County Commissioners, 1977-1978 (Box 61, Folder 16)
      - Republican County Commissioners for Thornburgh-Scranton, 1977-1978 (Box 61, Folder 17)
      - PSEA for Thornburgh-Scranton, 1977-1978 (Box 61, Folder 18)
      - Youth for Thornburgh-Scranton, 1977-1978 (Box 61, Folder 19)
      - Dentists for Thornburgh-Scranton, 1977-1978 (Box 61, Folder 20)
      - Farm and Rural Families for Thornburgh-Scranton, 1977-1978 (Box 61, Folder 21)
      - Democrats for Thornburgh-Scranton, 1977-1978 (Box 61, Folder 22)
      - Highway Industry Committee for Thornburgh-Scranton, 1977-1978 (Box 61, Folder 23)
      - Women for Thornburgh-Scranton, 1977-1978 (Box 61, Folder 24)
      - Regional Advisory Committees, 1977-1978 (Box 61, Folder 25)
      - Delaware Valley Regional Advisory Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 61, Folder 26)
      - Primary contributors, address lists, January-May, 1978 (Box 61, Folder 27)
      - County Commissioners, address lists, 1977-1978 (Box 61, Folder 28)
      - Delegates and alternates list, 1977-1978 (Box 61, Folder 29)
      - Farmers, address lists, 1977-1978 (Box 61, Folder 30)
      - "Friends," address lists, 1977-1978 (Box 61, Folder 31)
      - Philadelphia persons (from Sam Line), address lists, 1977-1978 (Box 61, Folder 32)
      - Republican County Chairmen and Vice-Chairmen, address lists, 1977-1978 (Box 61, Folder 33)
      - Teachers, address lists, 1977-1978 (Box 61, Folder 34)
      - Washington DC names, address lists, 1977-1978 (Box 61, Folder 35)
      - "Coffees" meetings: campaign tactic for meeting public and gaining dedicated supporters, 1977-1978 (Box 61, Folder 36)
      - Telephone bank, instructions and suggested conversations, 1977-1978 (Box 61, Folder 37)
      - Telephone bank, operation, plan, memos, 1977-1978 (Box 62, Folder 1)
      - "Get out the Vote" effort, 1977-1978 (Box 62, Folder 2)
      - Resumes, staff, 1977-1978 (Box 62, Folder 3)
      - Resumes, non-staff, recommendations, offers of help, 1977-1978 (Box 62, Folder 4)
      - "Thornburgh for Governor" committee mailings and brochures, 1977-1978 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - Volunteers
      - Pittsburgh primary efforts: plans and lists of names, January-May, 1978 (Box 62, Folder 6)
      - Master alpha file for Pittsburgh area volunteers, Primary, January-May, 1978 (Box 62, Folder 7)
      - County volunteer chairperson or research department list, Primary, January-May, 1978 (Box 62, Folder 8)
      - Master mailing list, Primary, January-May, 1978 (Box 62, Folder 9)
      - Allegheny County Republican Committee, list used to recruit volunteers, Primary, January-May, 1978 (Box 62, Folder 10)
      - Dorothy Larsen, Pittsburgh office volunteers, Primary, January-May, 1978 (Box 62, Folder 11)
      - Petitions, incomplete, Primary, January-May, 1978 (Box 63, Folder 1)
      - All committee members, address cards, Primary, January-May, 1978 (Box 63, Folder 2)
      - Organization and instructions, General, June-November, 1978 (Box 63, Folder 3)
      - Pittsburgh alpha list, General, June-November, 1978 (Box 63, Folder 4)
      - Thank you lists, Pittsburgh, General, June-November, 1978 (Box 63, Folder 5)
      - Pittsburgh area labels, General, June-November, 1978 (Box 63, Folder 6)
      - Oakmont phone bank lists, General, June-November, 1978 (Box 63, Folder 7)
      - Coffee and tea attendees, General, June-November, 1978 (Box 63, Folder 8)
      - Volunteer thank you letters, General, June-November, 1978 (Box 63, Folder 9)
      - Volunteer lists and phone bank schedules, 1977-1978 (Box 63, Folder 10)
      - Campaign schedules for volunteering and campaigning, 1977-1978 (Box 63, Folder 11)
      - Card file of Allegheny County volunteers, yellow tabs, Volunteers of 1978 not reached in 1982, 1977-1982 (Box 63, Folder 12)
      - Card file of Allegheny County volunteers, salmon dividers, Volunteers of 1978 reached in 1982, 1977-1982 (Box 63, Folder 13)
    - County Files
      - West Pennsylvania Counties, Primary, Bob Antonelli, January-May, 1978 (Box 63, Folder 14-15)
      - Southwest Counties, General, Bill Green, June-November, 1978 (Box 64, Folder 1-2)
      - Miscellaneous Counties, Primary, January-May, 1978 (Box 64, Folder 3-4)
      - Allegheny County, Primary, Districts 1-8, January-May, 1978 (Box 64, Folder 5-6)
      - Allegheny County, General, Municipalities A-M, Fernsler, June-November, 1978 (Box 64, Folder 7-9)
      - Allegheny County, General, Municipalities N-W, Fernsler, June-November, 1978 (Box 65, Folder 1-2)
      - County data and memos, incomplete, 1977-1978 (Box 65, Folder 3)
      - Adams County, 1977-1978 (Box 65, Folder 4)
      - Allegheny County, 1977-1978 (Box 65, Folder 5-6)
      - Armstrong County, 1977-1978 (Box 65, Folder 7)
      - Beaver County, 1977-1978 (Box 65, Folder 8)
      - Bedford County, 1977-1978 (Box 65, Folder 9)
      - Berks County, 1977-1978 (Box 65, Folder 10)
      - Blair County, 1977-1978 (Box 65, Folder 11)
      - Bradford County, 1977-1978 (Box 65, Folder 12)
      - Bucks County, 1977-1978 (Box 65, Folder 13)
      - Butler County, 1977-1978 (Box 65, Folder 14)
      - Cambria County, 1977-1978 (Box 65, Folder 15)
      - Cameron County, 1977-1978 (Box 65, Folder 16)
      - Carbon County, 1977-1978 (Box 65, Folder 17)
      - Centre County, 1977-1978 (Box 65, Folder 18)
      - Chester County, 1977-1978 (Box 65, Folder 19)
      - Clarion County, 1977-1978 (Box 66, Folder 1)
      - Clearfield County, 1977-1978 (Box 66, Folder 2)
      - Clinton County, 1977-1978 (Box 66, Folder 3)
      - Columbia County, 1977-1978 (Box 66, Folder 4)
      - Crawford County, 1977-1978 (Box 66, Folder 5)
      - Cumberland County, 1977-1978 (Box 66, Folder 6)
      - Dauphin County, 1977-1978 (Box 66, Folder 7)
      - Delaware County, 1977-1978 (Box 66, Folder 8)
      - Elk County, 1977-1978 (Box 66, Folder 9)
      - Erie County, 1977-1978 (Box 66, Folder 10-11)
      - Fayette County, 1977-1978 (Box 66, Folder 12)
      - Forest County, 1977-1978 (Box 66, Folder 13)
      - Franklin County, 1977-1978 (Box 66, Folder 14)
      - Fulton County, 1977-1978 (Box 66, Folder 15)
      - Greene County, 1977-1978 (Box 66, Folder 16)
      - Huntingdon County, 1977-1978 (Box 66, Folder 17)
      - Indiana County, 1977-1978 (Box 66, Folder 18)
      - Jefferson County, 1977-1978 (Box 66, Folder 19)
      - Juniata County, 1977-1978 (Box 66, Folder 20)
      - Lackawanna County, 1977-1978 (Box 66, Folder 21)
      - Lancaster County, 1977-1978 (Box 66, Folder 22)
      - Lawrence County, 1977-1978 (Box 66, Folder 23)
      - Lebanon County, 1977-1978 (Box 66, Folder 24)
      - Lehigh County, 1977-1978 (Box 67, Folder 1)
      - Luzerne County, 1977-1978 (Box 67, Folder 2)
      - Lycoming County, 1977-1978 (Box 67, Folder 3)
      - McKean County, 1977-1978 (Box 67, Folder 4)
      - Mercer County, 1977-1978 (Box 67, Folder 5)
      - Mifflin County, 1977-1978 (Box 67, Folder 6)
      - Monroe County, 1977-1978 (Box 67, Folder 7)
      - Montgomery County, 1977-1978 (Box 67, Folder 8)
      - Montour County, 1977-1978 (Box 67, Folder 9)
      - Northampton County, 1977-1978 (Box 67, Folder 10)
      - Northumberland County, 1977-1978 (Box 67, Folder 11)
      - Perry County, 1977-1978 (Box 67, Folder 12)
      - Philadelphia County, 1977-1978 (Box 67, Folder 13)
      - Pike County, 1977-1978 (Box 67, Folder 14)
      - Potter County, 1977-1978 (Box 67, Folder 15)
      - Schuylkill County, 1977-1978 (Box 67, Folder 16)
      - Snyder County, 1977-1978 (Box 67, Folder 17)
      - Somerset County, 1977-1978 (Box 67, Folder 18)
      - Sullivan County, 1977-1978 (Box 67, Folder 19)
      - Susquehanna County, 1977-1978 (Box 67, Folder 20)
      - Tioga County, 1977-1978 (Box 67, Folder 21)
      - Union County, 1977-1978 (Box 68, Folder 1)
      - Venango County, 1977-1978 (Box 68, Folder 2)
      - Warren County, 1977-1978 (Box 68, Folder 3)
      - Washington County, 1977-1978 (Box 68, Folder 4)
      - Wayne County, 1977-1978 (Box 68, Folder 5)
      - Westmoreland County, 1977-1978 (Box 68, Folder 6-7)
      - Wyoming County, 1977-1978 (Box 68, Folder 8)
      - York County, 1977-1978 (Box 68, Folder 9)
      - Regional Field Staff, Primary, January-May, 1978 (Box 68, Folder 10)
      - Regional Field Staff, Primary reports, January-May, 1978 (Box 68, Folder 11)
      - Regional Field Staff, General, June-November, 1978 (Box 68, Folder 12)
      - Regional Field Staff, General reports, June-November, 1978 (Box 68, Folder 13)
      - Organizational press releases, statewide and regional (persons named to assist with the campaign), 1977-1978 (Box 68, Folder 14)
      - Political activities, distribution of materials, 1977-1978 (Box 68, Folder 15)
      - Media Monitor reports, 1977-1978 (Box 68, Folder 16)
      - County maps, 1977-1978 (Box 68, Folder 17)
      - County Chairman's manual, Primary, January-May, 1978 (Box 68, Folder 18)
      - County statistics, party registration and election results for Primary, January-May, 1978 (Box 69, Folder 1)
      - Allegheny County, extra material, 1977-1978 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Scheduling
      - Memos, scheduling guidelines, George Whitmer, Eddie Mahe, examples from other campaigns, October 19, 1977; June 19, 1978 (Box 69, Folder 3)
      - Thornburgh sample letters/forms, 1977-1978 (Box 69, Folder 4)
      - Fairs, festivals, General, June-November, 1978 (Box 69, Folder 5)
      - Debate requests, General, June-November, 1978 (Box 69, Folder 6)
      - Ginny Thornburgh (VJT) schedules and remarks at GOP committee events, 1978 (Box 69, Folder 7)
      - Ginny Thornburgh (VJT): memos and schedules, list of appearances, 1977 early campaign speech, 1977-1978 (Box 69, Folder 8)
      - Bill Scranton (WWS III): schedules and form letters, 1977-1978 (Box 69, Folder 9)
      - Thornburgh schedule logs, November 14, 1977-October 30, 1978 (Box 69, Folder 10)
      - 1977 Schedule and calendar (Box 69, Folder 11)
      - Thornburgh's schedules, April 28, 1977-January 31, 1978 (Box 69, Folder 12)
      - Thornburgh's schedules, January 31, 1978-November 6, 1978 (Box 69, Folder 13)
      - Thornburgh weekly schedules, Primary, January-May, 1978 (Box 69, Folder 14)
      - Thornburgh monthly schedules (long range planning), Primary, July, 1977-May, 1978 (Box 69, Folder 15)
      - Thornburgh long range schedules, General, June-November, 1978 (Box 69, Folder 16)
      - Thornburgh alpha list of scheduled appearances (by organization), 1977-1978 (Box 69, Folder 17)
      - Thornburgh regrets, May, 1977-May 16, 1978 (Box 70, Folder 1-5)
      - Thornburgh miscellaneous thank you letters, Primary, January-May, 1978 (Box 70, Folder 6)
      - Thornburgh regrets, May 17-November 7, 1978 (Box 70, Folder 7-11)
    - Media
      - TV ads, 1977-1978 (Box 71, Folder 1)
      - Thornburgh and Scranton biographies (includes Coral Scranton), 1977-1978 (Box 71, Folder 2)
      - Family bios, speeches, correspondence, Thornburgh's Linden Avenue house memo, 1977-1978 (Box 71, Folder 3)
      - Thornburgh bios, accomplishments, 1977-1978 (Box 71, Folder 4)
      - Clippings: negative stories, 1977-1978 (Box 71, Folder 5)
      - Statewide Monitoring System, 1977-1978 (Box 71, Folder 6)
      - Thornburgh appearance requests: radio/TV/Newspapers, 1977-1978 (Box 71, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence, memos of Thornburgh and Paul Critchlow with press/reporters/special contacts, 1977-1978 (Box 71, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence of Assistant Press Secretaries Curt Ashenfelter and Patty McCormick, 1977-1978 (Box 71, Folder 9)
      - Radio actualities transcripts, 1977-1978 (Box 71, Folder 10)
        - Farmer's Town Meeting, Lancaster, April 13-14, 1978; 1.
        - Farmer's Town Meeting, Lancaster, April 15, 1978; 2.
        - Local rule in city government, April 18, 1978; 3.
        - Ethics legislation proposals, Harrisburg, April 19, 1978; 4.
        - Ethics in state government, April 20, 1978; 5.
        - Senior citizen property tax reform, April 27, 1978; 6.
        - Senior citizen property tax reform, May 2, 1978; 7.
        - Senator John Heinz's endorsement, May 4-5, 1978; 8.
        - State spending cap, July 24, 1978; 9.
        - State spending cap, July 25, 1978; 10.
        - Special prosecutor for PennDOT, August 18, 1978; 11.
        - Pete Flaherty fund raiser, September 1, 1978; 12.
        - "Waste Watchers", September 8, 1978; 13.
        - Housecleaning in Harrisburg, September 15, 1978; 14.
        - Housecleaning in Harrisburg, September 19, 1978; 15.
        - Time to talk sense about Pennsylvania's taxes: spending cap II, September 22, 1978; 16.
        - Time to talk sense about Pennsylvania's taxes: spending cap II, September 26, 1978; 17.
        - Pete Flaherty unfit to clean up corruption in Harrisburg, October 5, 1978; 18.
        - Integrity, 1978; 19.
        - Senior citizens, 1978; 20.
        - Children with Disabilities, 1978; 21.
        - Concerned Citizens, 1978; 22.
      - Radio ad transcripts, 1977-1978 (Box 71, Folder 11)
      - Printing costs, samples, correspondence (buttons, brochures, etc.), non-electric ad information, 1977-1978 (Box 71, Folder 12)
      - Mailing lists: news clips, press releases, long range schedules, 1977-1978 (Box 71, Folder 13)
      - Newspaper ads, 1977-1978 (Box 71, Folder 14)
      - Original lists for mailing labels: GOP chairmen, State Senators, Legislators, United States Congressional leaders, Thornburgh-Scranton chairmen, public opinion leaders, 1977-1978 (Box 71, Folder 15)
      - Original lists for mailing labels: Dailies, weeklies, TV and radio stations, other Pennsylvania media, 1977-1978 (Box 71, Folder 16)
      - Sample press kit for announcement, 1977-1978 (Box 71, Folder 17)
      - Sample press kit for Primary, January-May, 1978 (Box 71, Folder 18)
      - Sample press kit for Early General, June, 1978 (Box 71, Folder 19)
      - Sample press kit for General, June-November, 1978 (Box 71, Folder 20)
      - Surrogates: general information, memos and suggestions, 1977-1978 (Box 71, Folder 21)
      - Surrogates: master kit for speakers, 1977-1978 (Box 72, Folder 1)
      - Surrogates: actual speakers, memos regarding possible speakers, 1977-1978 (Box 72, Folder 2)
      - Surrogates: suggestions for speeches, 1977-1978 (Box 72, Folder 3)
      - Surrogates: requests fulfilled, 1977-1978 (Box 72, Folder 4)
      - Surrogates: requests pending, 1977-1978 (Box 72, Folder 5)
      - Sample surrogate kit, General, June-November, 1978 (Box 72, Folder 6)
      - Press and surrogate kits sent, 1977-1978 (Box 72, Folder 7)
      - Newspaper endorsements and thank you letters: General, June-November, 1978 (Box 72, Folder 8)
      - Lists of major Pennsylvania media, with addresses and phone numbers, 1977-1978 (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - Contributions
      - Plans and budgets: Primary (Evans Rose) and General (Jay Waldman), 1977-1978 (Box 72, Folder 10)
      - Financial disclosure: memos and clippings, 1977-1978 (Box 72, Folder 11)
      - Press releases regarding campaign contributions, January-December, 1978 (Box 72, Folder 12)
      - Press releases regarding campaign contributions, January-December, 1978 (Box 72, Folder 13)
      - Press releases regarding campaign contributions, January-December, 1978 (Box 72, Folder 14)
      - Evans Rose, memos to and from, re contributions, 1977-1978 (Box 72, Folder 15)
      - Farrell Rubenstein, memos and correspondence to and from, miscellaneous campaign staff expense lists, 1977-1978 (Box 73, Folder 1)
      - Fundraising: names, event lists, organization lists, contacts, Primary and General, 1977-1978 (Box 73, Folder 2)
      - 1978 and 1982 Contributors list, 150 dollars and larger, 1977-1978 (Box 73, Folder 3)
      - Letters and mailings requesting financial support, 1977-1978 (Box 73, Folder 4)
      - Thornburgh's to-do lists and phone calls-to-make lists, annotated notes, 1977-1978 (Box 73, Folder 5-6)
      - Contributions to Thornburgh campaign: miscellaneous correspondence regarding finances, fundraising events, enclosing contributions, 1977-1978 (Box 73, Folder 7)
      - Finance letters from Thornburgh, Woznisky, Rubenstein, 1977 (Box 73, Folder 8)
      - John Woznisky: letter and memos, 1978 (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence
      - Correspondence and Subject Files, Alphabetical"
        - A, 1977-1978 (Box 73, Folder 10)
        - B, 1977-1978 (Box 74, Folder 1)
        - C, 1977-1978 (Box 74, Folder 2)
        - D, 1977-1978 (Box 74, Folder 3)
        - E, 1977-1978 (Box 74, Folder 4)
        - F, 1977-1978 (Box 74, Folder 5)
        - G, 1977-1978 (Box 74, Folder 6)
        - H, 1977-1978 (Box 74, Folder 7)
        - I, 1977-1978 (Box 74, Folder 8)
        - J, 1977-1978 (Box 74, Folder 9)
        - K, 1977-1978 (Box 75, Folder 1)
        - L, 1977-1978 (Box 75, Folder 2)
        - M, 1977-1978 (Box 75, Folder 3)
        - N, 1977-1978 (Box 75, Folder 4)
        - O, 1977-1978 (Box 75, Folder 5)
        - P, 1977-1978 (Box 75, Folder 6)
        - Q, 1977-1978 (Box 75, Folder 7)
        - R, 1977-1978 (Box 75, Folder 8)
        - S, 1977-1978 (Box 75, Folder 9)
        - T, 1977-1978 (Box 75, Folder 10)
        - U, 1977-1978 (Box 76, Folder 1)
        - V, 1977-1978 (Box 76, Folder 2)
        - W, 1977-1978 (Box 76, Folder 3)
        - X, Y, Z, 1977-1978 (Box 76, Folder 4)
        - Law Firm materials, 1977-1978 (Box 76, Folder 5)
        - "Why Worry about Gambling ... Why not Concentrate on Something Important?" Law and Psychology Review paper by Governor Thornburgh, 1977-1978 (Box 76, Folder 6)
        - American Bar Foundation, 1977-1978 (Box 76, Folder 7)
        - Pennsylvania Bar Association, 1977-1978 (Box 76, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence, Groups, Alphabetical"
        - A, January, 1978- November, 1978 (Box 76, Folder 9)
        - B, January, 1978- November, 1978 (Box 76, Folder 10)
        - C, January, 1978- November, 1978 (Box 76, Folder 11)
        - E, January, 1978- November, 1978 (Box 76, Folder 12)
        - F, January, 1978- November, 1978 (Box 76, Folder 13)
        - G, January, 1978- November, 1978 (Box 76, Folder 14)
        - H, January, 1978- November, 1978 (Box 76, Folder 15)
        - I, January, 1978- November, 1978 (Box 76, Folder 16)
        - M, January, 1978- November, 1978 (Box 76, Folder 17)
        - N, January, 1978- November, 1978 (Box 76, Folder 18)
        - P, January, 1978- November, 1978 (Box 76, Folder 19)
        - R, January, 1978- November, 1978 (Box 76, Folder 20)
        - S, January, 1978- November, 1978 (Box 76, Folder 21)
        - U, January, 1978- November, 1978 (Box 76, Folder 22)
        - W, January, 1978- November, 1978 (Box 76, Folder 23)
      - Correspondence, Individuals, Alphabetical"
        - A, January, 1978- November, 1978 (Box 76, Folder 24)
        - B, January, 1978- November, 1978 (Box 76, Folder 25)
        - C, January, 1978- November, 1978 (Box 76, Folder 26)
        - D, January, 1978- November, 1978 (Box 76, Folder 27)
        - E, January, 1978- November, 1978 (Box 76, Folder 28)
        - F, January, 1978- November, 1978 (Box 76, Folder 29)
        - G, January, 1978- November, 1978 (Box 76, Folder 30)
        - H, January, 1978- November, 1978 (Box 76, Folder 31)
        - I, January, 1978- November, 1978 (Box 76, Folder 32)
        - J, January, 1978- November, 1978 (Box 77, Folder 1)
        - K, January, 1978- November, 1978 (Box 77, Folder 2)
        - L, January, 1978- November, 1978 (Box 77, Folder 3)
        - M, January, 1978- November, 1978 (Box 77, Folder 4)
        - N, January, 1978- November, 1978 (Box 77, Folder 5)
        - O, January, 1978- November, 1978 (Box 77, Folder 6)
        - P, January, 1978- November, 1978 (Box 77, Folder 7)